Guide to the Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Collection of Labor Movement Serials WAG.345
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: Labor unions and organizations, 1890-2012; 72.1 Linear Feet in 19 record cartons, 29 manuscript boxes, 2 half manuscript boxes, and 152 flat boxes
  - Subseries I.B: Communication Workers, 1914-2012; 22.1 Linear Feet in 8 record cartons, 11 manuscript boxes, and 34 flat boxes
    - Communique: Communications Workers of America - Local 6012, Tulsa, OK, 1986; cuid9987 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Communicator: Communications Workers of America - Local 6016, Oklahoma City, OK, 1986-1987; cuid9988 (Box 75, Folder 44)
    - Communicator: Communications Workers of America - Local 6143, San Antonio, TX, 1987; cuid9989 (Box 75, Folder 45)
    - Local 6171 News: Communications Workers of America - Local 6171, San Angelo, TX, 1986-1987; cuid9990 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Local 6171 News: Communications Workers of America - Local 6171, San Angelo, TX, 1986; cuid9991 (Box 172, Folder 68)
    - Organizer / Communications Workers of America. Local 6360: Communications Workers of America - Local 6360, Lee's Summit, Mo, 1974; cuid9992 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Alliance: Communications Workers of America - Local 7011, District 7, Albuquerque, NM, 1988; cuid9993 (Box 172, Folder 64)
    - Contact: Communications Workers of America - Local 7019, Phoenix, AZ, 1986; cuid9994 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Local Voice: Communications Workers of America - Local 7060, Phoenix, AZ, 1986; cuid9995 (Box 75, Folder 46)
    - Hotlines: Communications Workers of America - Local 7101, Cedar Rapids, IA, 1986-1987; cuid9996 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - CWA Bridge: Communications Workers of America - Local 7103, Sioux City, IA, 1986-1987; cuid9997 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - Newsletter: Communications Workers of America - Local 7108, Waterloo, IA, 1987; cuid9998 (Box 75, Folder 47)
    - Pact news: Communications Workers of America - Local 7200, Minneapolis, MN, 1987; cuid9999 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - PACT News: Communications Workers of America - Local 7200, Minneapolis, MN, 1986-1987; cuid10000 (Box 172, Folder 61)
    - Tie Line: Communications Workers of America - Local 7201, St. Paul, MN, 1986-1987; cuid10001 (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - Public Workers Operations News: Communications Workers of America - Local 7775, Denver, CO, 1986; cuid10002 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - 7777 Communicator: Communications Workers of America - Local 7777, Englewood, CO, 1986-1987; cuid10003 (Box 75, Folder 48)
    - 7790 Newsletter: Communications Workers of America - Local 7790, Denver, CO, 1986-1987; cuid10004 (Box 172, Folder 65)
    - CWA Way: Communications Workers of America - Local 7818, Spokane, WA, 1987; cuid10005 (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - Broadcast: Communications Workers of America - Local 7901, Portland, OR, 1987; cuid10006 (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - Livewire: Communications Workers of America - Local 7906/9206, Springfield, OR, 1986-1987; cuid10007 (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - Local 7970 News: Communications Workers of America - Local 7970, Hood River, OR, 1986-1987; cuid10008 (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - 8412 Communicator: Communications Workers of America - Local 8412, Englewood, CO, 1986; cuid10009 (Box 75, Folder 49)
    - Public Workers Operations News: Communications Workers of America - Local 8475, Denver, CO, 1986; cuid10010 (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - 8490 Newsletter: Communications Workers of America - Local 8490, Denver, CO, 1985; cuid10011 (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - Contact: Communications Workers of America - Local 8519, Phoenix, AZ, 1986; cuid10012 (Box 162, Folder 28)
    - CWA Evergreen Edition: Communications Workers of America - Local 9112, Vancouver, WA, 1986; cuid10013 (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - Local 9270 News: Communications Workers of America - Local 9270, Hood River, OR, 1986; cuid10014 (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - Local News: Communications Workers of America - Local 9413, Reno, NV, 1986; cuid10015 (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - Voice: Communications Workers of America - Local 9415, Oakland, CA, 1976; cuid10016 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Cross Talk: Communications Workers of America - Local 9417, Stockton, CA, 1986; cuid10017 (Box 75, Folder 50)
    - Positive View: Communications Workers of America - Local 9421, Sacramento, CA, 1985; cuid10018 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - CWA Newsletter: Communications Workers of America - Local 9490, Pacifica, CA, 1986; cuid10019 (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - C.W.A. Communique 9503: Communications Workers of America - Local 9503, Chatsworth, CA, 1987; cuid10020 (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - Appriser: Communications Workers of America - Local 9505, Arcadia, CA, 1986; cuid10021 (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - Local Motion: Communications Workers of America - Local 9573, San Bernadino, CA, 1986-1987; cuid10022 (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - Breeze: Communications Workers of America - Local 9586, Santa Fe Springs, CA, 1987; cuid10023 (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - Inter-com: Communications Workers of America - Locals 3112-3111, West Palm Beach, FL, 1979; cuid10024 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Voice - Long Lines: Communications Workers of America - Long Lines Members, New York, NY, 1980; cuid10025 (Box 172, Folder 6)
    - Michigan Communication Worker: Communications Workers of America - Michigan Division 15, Detroit, MI, 1949-1950; cuid10026 (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - Militant Action: Communications Workers of America - Militant Action Caucus, El Cerrito, CA, 1974; cuid10027 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Bulletin: Communications Workers of America - Municipal Management Society of Local 1180, New York, NY, 1968-1971, 1973; cuid10028 (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - MMS Voice: Communications Workers of America - Municipal Management Society of Local 1180, New York, NY, 1968; cuid10029 (Box 2, Folder 64)
    - Newsletter: Communications Workers of America - Municipal Management Society of Local 1180, New York, NY, 1972-1976; cuid10030 (Box 1, Folder 68)
    - State Worker: Communications Workers of America - New Jersey State Worker Locals, Newark, NJ, 1989-1991; cuid10031 (Box 2, Folder 65-66)
    - Coast Coordinator: Communications Workers of America - Pacific Coast Area, 1951, 1953; cuid10032 (Box 2, Folder 67)
    - Newsletter: Communications Workers of America - Retired Members Club, Cleveland, Cleveland, OH, 1986; cuid10033 (Box 172, Folder 63)
    - Cable: Communications Workers of America - Sales Division 18, New York, NY, 1950; cuid10034 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Cable Rack: Communications Workers of America - Southern Local 3290, Atlanta, Ga, 1969, 1975; cuid10035 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - In Brief: Communications Workers of America (AFL-CIO), 1984-1984; cuid10036 (Box 2, Folder 68)
    - Communications: Communications Workers of America's ATT-Communications National Bargaining Unit, Somerset, NJ, 1985; cuid10037 (Box 2, Folder 69)
    - Technologies: Communications Workers of America's ATT-Communications National Bargaining Unit, Somerset, NJ, 1985; cuid10038 (Box 2, Folder 70)
    - Bulletin of the Correlated Graphic Industries, inc: Correlated Graphic Industries, New York, NY, 1932; cuid10039 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Critical Times: Critical Times Newspaper Collective - New American Movement, Philadelphia, PA, 1973-1974; cuid10040 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - CWA Proud of Our Past Prepared for Tomorrow: Reports and Proceedings: CWA- Communication Workers of America, San Francisco, CA, 1985 (Box 197, Folder 4-5)
    - CWA Security '83: Daily Reports and Proceedings: CWA- Communication Workers of America, Los Angeles, CA, 1983 (Box 194, Folder 5-6)
    - Daily Reports and Proceedings: 44th Annual Convention: CWA- Communication Workers of America, Detroit, MI, 1983 (Box 195, Folder 1-4)
    - Commitee on the Future: CWA- Communication Workers of America, Washington, DC, 1983 (Box 194, Folder 3)
    - Write Up: Detroit-Metro Chapter UPSurge, Detroit, MI, 1976; cuid10041 (Box 1, Folder 69)
    - District Three Leader / International Union of Electrical, Radio & Machine Workers: District Three Union IUE-AFL-CIO, East Rutherford, NJ, 1969 (Box 211, Folder 1)
    - AUTW News Bulletin: Editorial Department of the American Union of Telephone Workers, New York, NY, 1946; cuid10042 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Horizons '76: Educational and Cultural Fund of the Electrical Industry, Flushing, NY, 1976; cuid10043 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Our Industry's Mosaic: Educational and Cultural Fund of the Electrical Industry, Flushing, NY, 1993; cuid10044 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - A.P. Review: Employees of the Associated Press, 1970; cuid10045 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Unidad: Federacion de Trabajadores Telefonicos de Cuba en el Exilio, Miami, FL, 1986; cuid10046 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - FTR News: Federal Telephone and Radio Corporation, Newark, NJ, 1946; cuid10047 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Final Warning: Final Warning, New York, N.Y., 1972-1975; cuid10048 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Guild Voice: Gary Newspaper Guild, Gary, IN, 1980; cuid10049 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Working People's Voice: Graphic Communications International Union, New York, NY, 2005; cuid10050 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Newspaper Worker: Inter-American Federation of Working Newspapermen's Organizations, 1962; cuid10051 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - IBEW: International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Washington, DC, 1981; cuid10052 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Local Union Directory: International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Washington, DC, 1979; cuid10053 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Utility Reporter: International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers - Local Union 1245, Walnut Creek, CA, 1989-1992; cuid10054 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Reporter: International Labor Communications Association, 2003; cuid10055 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - American Photo-Engraver Readers' Guide: International Photo Engravers Union, Chicago, IL, Undated (Box 200, Folder 1)
    - Wages and Profits in Wartime: International Publishers, New York, NY, 1941 (Box 180, Folder 25)
    - Appeal: International Typographical Union - New York Local No. 6, New York, NY, 1963; cuid10056 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Bulletin (Supplement): International Typographical Union, 1947; cuid10057 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Changes in the Laws Adopted by the One Hundred Nineteenth Convention of the International Typographical Union: International Typographical Union, Cincinnati, OH, 1978 (Box 200, Folder 2)
    - Pension Plan: International Typographical Union, 1988; cuid10058 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Proceedings of the One Hundred Twenty-Second Convention of the International Typographical Union: International Typographical Union, Kansas City, Missouri, 1980 (Box 200, Folder 12)
    - Review: International Typographical Union, Colorado Springs, CO, 1984 (Box 193, Folder 8)
    - I.T.U. News: International Typographical Union - Executive Council, 1944; cuid10059 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - ITU Review: International Typographical Union - Executive Council, Colorado Springs, CO, 1965, 1978; cuid10060 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - ITU Review: International Typographical Union - Executive Council, Colorado Springs, CO, 1964-1984; cuid10061 (Box 6, Folder 16-17)
    - IUE-CWA News: International Union of Electric, Electrical, Salaried, Machine and Furniture Workers - Communication Workers of America, Washington, DC, circa 1970s; cuid10062 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - History and Organization of the Joint Industry Board of the Electrical Industry: Joint Industry Board of the Electrical Industry, 1993; cuid10063 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Proceedings: International Union of Electrical Radio and Machine Workers, Milwaukee, WI, 1950 (Box 200, Folder 9)
    - Los Angeles Guildsman: Los Angeles Newspaper Guild - Local 69, Los Angeles, CA, 1952; cuid10064 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Memo to Mailers: Memo to Mailers, Washington, DC, 1991; cuid10065 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Detroit Union: Metropolitan Detroit Council of Newspaper Unions, Detroit, MI, circa 1970s; cuid10066 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Metrospect: Metropolitan New York Labor Press Council, New York, NY, 1995; cuid10067 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Tie Lines: Michigan Bell, Detroit, MI, 1976; cuid10068 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Newsletter: Mid-Altantic Conference of Printers and Mailers, Baltimore, MD, 1987; cuid10069 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - The Ring Knife: Missoula, Montana Postal Workers, Missoula, MT, 1987; cuid10070 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - L'aiguille: Montreal Joint Board, Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America (CLC-AFL-CIO), Montreal, Canada, 1967; cuid10072 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Guild Bulletin: Montreal Newspaper Guild, Montreal, Canada, circa 1970s; cuid10073 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - POV (NABET 15): National Association of Broadcast Employees and Technicians - Local 15, 1985; cuid10074 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Local 15 In Focus: National Association of Broadcast Employees and Technicians - Local No. 15, New York, NY, 1990; cuid10075 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - NABET News: National Association of Broadcast Employees & Technicians, Montreal, Quebec, 1974-1979 (Box 197, Folder 9, Box 222, Folder 14-16)
    - NABET News: National Association of Broadcast Employees & Technicians, Chicago, IL, 1956-1972 (Box 222, Folder 6-12, Box 223, Folder 1-2)
    - NABET 15 Spotlight: National Association of Broadcast Employees & Technicians (NABET), Boston, MA, 1986 (Box 183, Folder 14)
    - NABET News: National Association of Broadcast Employees & Technicians, AFL-CIO, Washington, DC, 1995-1996 (Box 219, Folder 7)
    - CIO News NABET Edition: National Association of Broadcast Employees and Technicians, Chicago, IL, 1954-1955 (Box 197, Folder 3, Box 223)
    - Nouvelles NABET: National Association of Broadcast Employees and Technicians, Montreal, Quebec, 1961-1973 (Box 222, Folder 1-4)
    - Bulletin: National Association of Letter Carriers, Washington, DC, 1954-1955; cuid10076 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Capitol Notes / National Association of Letter Carriers: National Association of Letter Carriers, Washington, DC, 1980-1984; cuid10077 (Box 173, Folder 11)
    - Postmark Washington: National Association of Letter Carriers, Washington, DC, 1985-1988; cuid10078 (Box 83, Folder 9)
    - NALC Activist Cumulative Index: National Association of Letter Carriers Information Center, Washington, DC, 1996; cuid10079 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Postal Transport Journal: National Postal Transport Association, Washington, DC, 1956; cuid10080 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Progressive: National Postal Union, Washington, DC, 1959, 1961-1971; cuid10081 (Box 3, Folder 34, Box 150, Folder 11-12, Box 160, Folder 10)
    - American Writer: National Writers Union, Washington, DC, 1987-1996 (Box 186, Folder 1, Box 223, Folder 4)
    - Spotlight: New York Newspaper Guild - Rank & File of the New York Newspaper Guild, New York, NY, 1949, 1980-1982; cuid10082 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Strike Update: New York Newspaper Printing Pressmen's Union - No. 2, New York, NY, 1990; cuid10083 (Box 172, Folder 5)
    - Number Six Bulletin: New York Typographical Union, New York, NY, 1985; cuid10084 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Typographical Union: New York Typographical Union - No. 6, New York, NY, 1970; cuid10085 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Guild News: Newspaper Guild (AFL-CIO), Philadelphia, PA, 1977; cuid10086 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Let's Talk Shop: Newspaper Guild Consumers Union Unit, 1980-1982; cuid10087 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Guilder: Newspaper Guild of Albany, NY, Albany, NY, 1981-1982; cuid10088 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Guild Memo: Newspaper Guild of Detroit Local 22, AFL-CIO, Detroit, MI, 1948; cuid10089 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Guild Memo: Newspaper Guild of Detroit Local 22, AFL-CIO, Detroit, MI, 1979; cuid10090 (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Local 3 Bulletin: Newspaper Guild of New York, 1979-1985; cuid10091 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - New York Guildpaper: Newspaper Guild of New York, New York, NY, 1942-1944, 1946; cuid10092 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Speaking Up: Newspaper Guild of New York - American Journal of Nursing, 1981; cuid10093 (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - City Desk: Newspaper Guild of New York - Amsterdam News Unit, 1981-1983; cuid10094 (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Guild Brooklyn Eagle: Newspaper Guild of New York - Brooklyn Eagle Unit, New York, NY, 1955; cuid10095 (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - Talk of 42nd St.: Newspaper Guild of New York - Daily News Unit, 1981-1983; cuid10096 (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - Hot Tips!: Newspaper Guild of New York - Daily Racing Form, 1982; cuid10097 (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - El Diario-La Prensa Guild Bulletin: Newspaper Guild of New York - El Diario-La Prensa Unit, 1982; cuid10098 (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - Watch on the Raritan: Newspaper Guild of New York - New Brunswick Home News Unit, 1979, 1981; cuid10099 (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - Times Topics: Newspaper Guild of New York - New York Times Unit, 1975, 1977-1981; cuid10100 (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - Union Times: Newspaper Guild of New York - New York Times Unit, 1981-1985; cuid10101 (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - Tribune Times: Newspaper Guild of New York - News Tribune Unit, New York, NY, 1982; cuid10102 (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - News Angles: Newspaper Guild of New York - News Unit, 1971, 1979-1981; cuid10103 (Box 3, Folder 53)
    - News Shop Paper: Newspaper Guild of New York - News Unit, New York, NY, 1947; cuid10104 (Box 3, Folder 54)
    - Newsweek Guild Bulletin: Newspaper Guild of New York - Newsweek Unit, 1980, 1982-1983; cuid10105 (Box 3, Folder 55)
    - News Unlimited: Newspaper Guild of New York - Post Unit, 1984; cuid10106 (Box 3, Folder 56)
    - South St. Other: Newspaper Guild of New York - Post Unit, 1979-1983; cuid10107 (Box 3, Folder 57)
    - Guildside: Newspaper Guild of New York - Republican-American Unit, 1979-1980; cuid10108 (Box 3, Folder 58)
    - Common Sense: Newspaper Guild of New York - Reuters Unit, 1979-1983; cuid10109 (Box 3, Folder 59)
    - Facts and Forum: Newspaper Guild of New York - Scholastic Unit, 1979-1982; cuid10110 (Box 3, Folder 60)
    - Spotlight: Newspaper Guild of New York - Standard & Poor's Unit, circa 1970s; cuid10111 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Guild Telegram and Sun: Newspaper Guild of New York - World-Telegram and Sun Unit, New York, NY, 1950; cuid10112 (Box 87, Folder 3, Box 173, Folder 13)
    - Truth: Newspaper Guild of New York - World-Telegram Unit, New York, NY, 1934; cuid10113 (Box 3, Folder 61)
    - Guild Progressive: Newspaper Guild of NYC - Independent Progressive Members of the Newspaper Guild of NYC, New York, NY, 1940; cuid10114 (Box 173, Folder 12)
    - Byline: Newspaper Reporters Association, New York, NY, 1965; cuid10115 (Box 3, Folder 62)
    - Spark: NJ-NJ United Workers Organization Electrical Committee, New York, NY, 1977; cuid10116 (Box 3, Folder 63)
    - APT Connections: North Carolina Department of Administration - Agency for Public Telecommunications, Raleigh, NC, 1990; cuid10117 (Box 3, Folder 64)
    - Work Life: Ohio Bell, Cleveland, OH, 1987; cuid10118 (Box 3, Folder 65)
    - Pacific Northwest Newspaper Guild: Pacific Northwest Newspaper Guild, 1979-1981; cuid10119 (Box 3, Folder 66)
    - PLP Flash: People's Labor Party, Cambridge, MA, 1937; cuid10120 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Back Grounder: Portland Newspaper Guild, Portland, ME, 1979; cuid10121 (Box 3, Folder 67)
    - Postal Action: Bulletin of the Postal Action Committee: Postal Action Committee, circa 1970s; cuid10122 (Box 3, Folder 68)
    - "The Struggle Continues:" Address by Jean-Claude Parrot, National President, Canadian Union of Postal Workers: Postal Workers Defense Committee, Jersey City, NJ, 1979; cuid10123 (Box 3, Folder 69)
    - Fight for a Good Contract: Postal Workers for a Good Contract, circa 1970s; cuid10124 (Box 3, Folder 70)
    - Postal Workers Voice: Postal Workers Voice, Hoboken, NJ, 1977; cuid10125 (Box 3, Folder 71)
    - Postal Workers Voice: Postal Workers Voice, Hoboken, NJ, 1977; cuid10126 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Postal Bulletin: Postmaster General, Washington, DC, 1954; cuid10127 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Phone Workers' News: PT&T, Undated (Box 181, Folder 5)
    - 1212 News: Radio, TV and Broadcast Engineers, Local 1212 IBEW, AFL-CIO, New York, NY, 1993; cuid10128 (Box 3, Folder 72)
    - Rank and File Postal Worker: Rank and File Postal Worker, Philadelphia, PA, 1976; cuid10129 (Box 1, Folder 70)
    - On Strike, Shut It Down: San Francisco State Strike Committee, circa 1980s; cuid10130 (Box 3, Folder 73)
    - Bay Guild News: San Francisco-Oakland Newspaper Guild, 1980; cuid10131 (Box 3, Folder 74)
    - Bay Guildsman: San Francisco-Oakland Newspaper Guild, San Francisco, CA, 1958, 1976; cuid10132 (Box 3, Folder 75)
    - S.O.N.G. Sheet: Southern Ontario Newspaper Guild, Toronto, Canada, 1979, 1981; cuid10133 (Box 3, Folder 76)
    - Officers' Report: State, County & Municipal Workers of America, Lansing, MI, 1941; cuid10134 (Box 3, Folder 77)
    - TIU News / Telecommunications International Union: Telecommunications International Union, Hamden, CT, 1985; cuid10135 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Telephone Pioneer: Telephone Pioneers of America, New York, NY, 1990; cuid10136 (Box 3, Folder 78)
    - Big Apple Newsletter: Telephone Pioneers of America/Big Apple Life Member Club, New York, NY, 1990; cuid10137 (Box 3, Folder 79)
    - Laying it on the Line: Telephone Workers, New York, NY, circa 1980s; cuid10138 (Box 3, Folder 80)
    - Texas AFL-CIO Labor News: Texas AFL-CIO, Austin, TX, 1986; cuid10139 (Box 3, Folder 81)
    - Update: Texas State Employees Union, Austin, TX, 1986; cuid10140 (Box 3, Folder 82)
    - Industrial Leader: The Industrial Leader Publishing Co., Winston-Salem, NC, 1937; cuid10141 (Box 3, Folder 83)
    - New Lead: Toronto Newspaper Guild, Toronto, Canada, 1967; cuid10142 (Box 3, Folder 84)
    - Traffic Jam: Traffic Jam, New York, NY, 1972 (Box 181, Folder 13)
    - True North: True North Communications, Saskatoon, Canada, 1992; cuid10143 (Box 3, Folder 85)
    - Wage Chronology: American Telephone and Telegraph Company - Long Lines Department, and Communications Workers of America (AFL-CIO), October 1940-July 1974: U.S. Department of Labor Bureau of Labor Statistics, Washington, DC (Box 199, Folder 15)
    - Union Advocate: Union Advocate newspaper, Inc., St. Paul, MN, 1992, 1994; cuid10144 (Box 3, Folder 86)
    - Steward Update: Union Communication Services, Inc., Annapolis, MD, 1990-1991, 1994-1996, 2003, undated; cuid10145 (Box 3, Folder 87)
    - Steward Update: Union Communication Services, Inc., Annapolis, MD, 2003 (Box 180, Folder 23)
    - Dial: United Brotherhood of Telephone Workers, 1939-1940, 1946; cuid10146 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Protecting Workers Health and Welfare: United Electrical, Radio & Machine Workers of America, Chicago, IL, 1949; cuid10147 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Shop News: United Electrical, Radio & Machine Workers of America, CIO, Brooklyn, NY, 1943; cuid10148 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - UE: United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America, circa 1980s; cuid10149 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - United Paperworkers' Corporate Campaign News: United Paperworkers International Union Local 6288, De Pere, WI, circa 1970s; cuid10150 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Photo Flashes: United Photographic Employees - Local Industrial Union #415, New York, NY, 1939; cuid10151 (Box 172, Folder 9)
    - Arkansas Union Labor Bulletin: United Publishing Co., Little Rock, AK, 1958; cuid10152 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - U.T.O. News: Official Journal United Telephone Organizations: United Telephone Organizations, New York, NY, 1949-1958; cuid10153 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Unity Slate: Unity Slate, Levittown, NY, 1979; cuid10154 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Inside Story: Vancouver/New Westminster Newspaper Guild, Vancouver, Canada, 1980; cuid10155 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Washington-Baltimore Newspaper Guild: Washington-Baltimore Newspaper Guild, circa 1970s; cuid10156 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Guild Forum: Washington-Baltimore Newspaper Guild Local 35 TNG, AFL-CIO, CLC, Washington, DC, 1978-1981, 1987; cuid10157 (Box 4, Folder 9)